Every time the rain no longer
falls, and I see the sky,
I think back to when I was
a child Who could only cry,
blindly chasing after
him I fell far behind
my only thought One day I will be stronger
Bridery and gratitude fading with the
wind Am I stronger now than I was before?
Or as weak as back then?
I don't know for sure, but until I do.
My voyage will not end.
No matter what's next.
I'm walking straight ahead.
So let's go.
There's nothing that can stop us now.
Though time's all on our side.
We'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall.
But we'll always keep on standing.
There's no way anything.
Will take what I hold dear away from me.
The voices inside me.
Push me to keep surviving.
I'll go on, I'll get through.
No matter what I gotta do.
The fiercest of the ball can pour upon me.
I don't care why in the
world would I turn back.
So let's go.
There's nothing that can stop us now.
Though time's not on our side.
We'll never let it pull us down.
And we may fall.
But we'll always keep on standing.
There's no way anything.
Will take what I hold dear away from me.
I know the future's there for us to see.
I
No, it can't be!
Whitebeard has been stabbed!
The old guy.
Why?
No, who stabbed him?
They'll be torn apart.
Wait, look.
It was one of Whitebeard's
allies who did it.
A captain from the New World.
The Whirlspider.
How dare you, Sward?
Why the hell did you attack Pops, huh?
Answer me now or I'll kill you.
Yeah? Then do it.
This whole mess is his fault anyway.
What do you mean?
Do you even realize what
you've just done, you...
Don't move, Pops.
You'll make things worse
if you keep squirming.
Whitebeard.
I'm serious.
This battle is a fake.
Just ask him.
I know about your treacherous
deal with the Navy.
You have their assurance that Ace and all
of your pirates won't even get scratched.
They'll just go after your allies.
Wait, what's he saying?
Is it true that they're just targeting us?
Everybody, listen up!
All this time you've kept it a secret.
You didn't have the
guts to tell me that Ace
is actually the son of that
wretched pirate, Gold Roger.
When you first found me,
I was alone in this world.
A complete wreck.
Sport is out of his mind again.
Isn't there anyone
strong enough to face me?
I'm right here.
Bring it on.
How's about Gold Roger?
Where's he at?
What's the matter?
Are you all scared?
Give me your best shot.
You knew why I was all alone that day.
My precious crew, who had fought
alongside me in so many battles,
was killed by Gold Roger.
You know this, and you know that I
despise Roger more than anything!
Yet you still kept these secrets
from me, that Ace was Roger's son,
that you were helping him become
the next king of the pirates?
How can I trust someone like you?
Never mind the Whitebeards!
Take care of yourselves!
Get back down to the plaza!
The old guy, he wants Ace to be the king.
Because you see, Whitebeard's the
greatest pirate I've ever met.
That's why I'm going to help
him become king of the pirates.
You've been betraying me and playing
me for a fool since the very beginning.
I didn't have a damn clue.
I bet you laughed your ass off
when I became friends with Ace.
Then your favorite son got caught,
and you showed your true colors.
All of the white-beard
pirates are inside the bay,
while us allied pirates are stuck outside.
Forty-three captains fight beside you,
and you handed us all to the Navy,
just to protect Roger's son.
We allied pirates will be obliterated.
Whereas Ace and your men
will be completely safe?
That's your underhanded
deal with Sengoku, isn't it?
That's enough!
We'll see who ends up dead, you wretch!
You're a stubborn brat!
But you'll learn what I'm
talking about soon enough?
Stand up and look for yourself.
We plan to converge our forces soon.
Then attack the allied pirates, only them.
And Whitebeard, the Navy isn't even going
to lay a finger on his gang of pirates.
Not one of us knew the truth.
And so, we followed you, risking
our lives to help rescue Ace.
Only to find out we were nothing
more than sacrifices to you!
We're the ones bearing the
brunt of the Navy's attacks!
It's as clear as day!
Those monsters approach from the back,
and the ice blocks us on both sides!
There's no way we can escape!
Wipe there! Old buddy!
Is he telling the truth?!
He's lying his teeth off!
He's gotta be!
It's a miracle I was able to stab you.
Well, now it's your turn!
Kill me!
He was right! Look!
The Navy's only going after us!
Run away!
Oh, buddy, please tell me we're not throwing
our lives away just so you can save us.
Please, say something, anything! Wipe me!
It can't be true it's
impossible white beard
wouldn't sell out fellow
pirates he did that!
To his allies no way he'd
fight the navy head on white
beard and the navy are in cahoots
all those new world pirates
who trusted and followed white
beard i know i can't believe
it they're all rushing to their
doom next to his betrayal i
didn't want to believe it we're
all sons to you but i guess
some kids are just worth more
than others you're a damn fool
the navy is deceiving you
squad why trust them instead of
pops i know you're in on the
deal don't you play dumb with me
you're the first division commander you're
basically white beard's right hand man if
anyone knows about his
deal with the navy it's
you it ain't ace's
fault his old man killed
squad's crew but it is
what it is and i can
only blame myself for
keeping it a secret all
these years the navy
made the right move that
doesn't make you any
less of a bastard though?
Sengoku even if you are a crafty one.
It's time to win this.
Go Aokiji!
Oh no!
Don't talk it off!
This entire war is a setup?
It can't seriously be fake!
I've wasted my whole
day watching this stuff.
It shut off! What's wrong? Is it broken?
Now activate the walls. Right.
The pirate who defeated me would
never be struck down so easily?
especially by his own ally.
You're not worth my time anymore, old man!
If this is how the Great Whitebeard
dies, you'll make a fool of us both!
Oh boy, that was harsh.
Then it was a matter of pride.
It's true.
He could have easily blocked that
if he was as tough as he used to be.
It wouldn't have mattered
that it was a surprise attack,
or that it came from one of his allies.
Anyways, has Pops gotten weaker than
we thought, and I just didn't notice?
I don't want no sympathy.
There's no way I'm wearing this
crap in front of my enemies.
What, Pops?
He's letting his health
get worse and worse.
I don't know if you realize the magnitude
of what you've just done, Squared.
You thrust a sword into your
father's body trying to kill him.
You've lost your way, my poor stupid son.
But I still love you, even
if you are a damn fool.
Cut the crap.
You've sold our lives out.
All of us.
Who took your loyal and
steadfast heart away from your
father and delivered it into
the hands of our enemies?
Now you tell me his name.
Aka 'inu.
Admiral Aka 'inu.
I'm opposed to such an underhanded plan.
The one we should kill in
this war is Whitebeard.
Letting him live would be a
great disservice to the world.
If you can help me, I'll save
all of the New World pirates.
Whitebeard, kill him.
He said if I killed you, he
would save your new world allies.
Akainu, so that's what he told you.
I completely understand how
much you hate Gold Roger.
So much so that I can feel your pain.
But listen to me.
It's ridiculous to lay the blame on
a child for the sins of his father.
Did Ace ever do a thing to hurt you?
The two of you have been
through so much together.
Some of it happy, some of it painful.
But you've weathered it all, good times
and bad, with our brothers in arms.
I never gave a damn about who
Ace's father is, and I still don't.
We all crossed paths on
these seas by chance.
And wherever the hell we came
from doesn't mean a thing anymore.
We're together now.
So, squad, please treat him kindly.
I don't love Ace more than
any other son of mine.
On that you have my word.
Every single one of you
is part of my family.
Now, moving on.
That's Sengoku.
He hasn't changed one bit.
The bastard.
But that crafty old snake gave us
a pretty good shake-up, didn't he?
But to even suggest that I'd
sell out my sons is ridiculous
They can leave now.
He destroyed the ice wall.
He's a sharp one.
There's nothing blocking
our path. You're right.
We can take these Navy ships
and sail away whenever we want.
If you're a true pirate, then you
choose which path to take on your own.
I knew it was a lie.
The Navy's just trying to tear us apart!
Come on guys, let's take it to them.
Of course they were lying, Old
Buddy would never betray us?
Hear that?
We'll die before we
ever lose trust in you,
Old Buddy Please forgive
me, we were wrong.
I'll follow you to the
end, White Beard Old Buddy.
Think I'm going soft do
you give it a rest Krieg
bum I'm only human and
every human has a heart
no matter how large or
small people can call me
a monster all they want
but the reality is I can't
be the strongest pirate
forever if I can save this
one young man's life I'll
have earned the right
to retire from this world
once and for all those
of you who will still
follow me put your lives on
Get ready, man!
He's coming his way!
The strongest pirate in the world!
Let's attack!
Don't let them get any closer! Fire!
We're with you all the way.
Clear a path.
Let's do this.
He's too strong.
He swore to me Pops would betray us.
Damn you squad!
How the hell could he let the
Navy trick him into stabbing Pops?
Does that fool really
think he would turn on us?
How could you do this!
Think of how Pops must feel!
If I was lied to
then what I've done what I've done to Pops
it's unforgivable!
I'm so sorry Pops!
forgive me Ace! please? Please!
Hey, Secret!
Pull it together.
Tears won't fix what you've done.
That old man's tough.
He gets stabbed and he's still at it!
I gotta get serious and save Ace!
Off we go!
Hey, Gene Bay!
Doesn't that strike you as odd?
They all abandoned their posts and retreated
to the plaza while we weren't looking.
Hmm.
Indeed, that is a bit troubling.
But old white beard has
joined the fray now.
That ought to put our worries to rest.
True.
We can handle whatever dirty
tricks they throw at us.
Fire on the walls up.
I'm sorry, sir.
We're trying.
But the ice is a lot
thicker than we thought.
I'll make you pay!
The wall is the crux of our plan.
This is bad.
I'm gonna buy us some
time till they fix it.
That's as far as you're gonna get.
You'll never reach the plaza!
Run!
My Sandmo John Giant is attacking!
You're blocking my view. Move.
What did he do?
Vice Admiral!
What?
Why is the ground tilting?
Everyone, keep your distance from Pops!
It's even worse than an earthquake!
This can't be real.
This is insane.
It's not just the island.
The entire sea is tilting.
That old SOB sure got some style.
I've got you!
Jinbei!
Hang on, I'll pull you up!
Thanks, Team Bay.
I owe you again.
Take me when this is over.
Is that crazy old man trying
to get his own crew killed?
No, his crew was ready.
They're used to this kind of thing.
One man did this?
He really is the strongest pirate alive.
I've never seen such
fierce a power before,
but in the name of the absolute
justice I've sworn to uphold,
I'd rather die than let
you pass through here!
It's headed right for us!
The shockwave's gonna hit the scaffold!
Yeah! Tear it apart!
What happened?
It looked like a direct hit.
But did we get it?
Doesn't look like it even touched the
scaffold so did something block the blast?
Do you see that?
It's the three admirals.
This mess wouldn't have happened
if the walls were ready.
Whose fault is that?
Your ice is blocking them.
Sure but you could have just
melted the ice couldn't you?
Let's go.
Give them hell!
White Beard! Pirates!
Sounds like they're pretty
pissed off down there?
Scary!
I want an update on the walls!
Uh They're still down.
Endeavor the energy that's
flowing into the city.
Pump every ounce of power into the walls.
Sir, right away.
Almost there, Ace!
Luffy!
I'm coming for you!
I'll save you!
Activating full power!
What is that?
What?
The walls!
They've closed us in!
What the hell's going on?
Take this!
Will daddy break?
What?
Oh man, not a scratch.
That's gotta be some
seriously thick steel.
I don't know about you guys,
but I'm pretty sure these are the
walls they were talking about.
Come on!
Are you too scared to fight us?
Hey look up there they've got an
arsenal of cannons locked on us we
gotta run they've got us locked
in there isn't any place for us to
except there what's going on down
there why did it the last wall
rage well it's uh it's oar's body
the walls don't seem strong enough
to lift it, sir.
Also, it looks like his blood is running
into the system and making it malfunction.
Damn beast.
Ores, you saved them.
Now that's a noble death.
He may be dead, but he's still fighting.
Impressive, huh?
Huh?
You've given us a chance, Ours.
We must be swift.
You know what to do, Aka 'inu.
Meteor Volcano!
That's it! We're finished!
They've got nowhere to run.
Now we'll melt that
ice and drown them all!